conversation	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
brings	O
you	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
clinic	B-ORGANIZATION
today	O
,	O
miss	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
refill	O
of	O
my	O
blood	B-HISTORY
pressure	I-HISTORY
medicine	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
Kumar	I-PERSON
followed	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
with	O
you	O
last	O
time	O
regarding	O
your	O
hypertension	B-HISTORY
,	O
osteoarthritis	B-HISTORY
,	O
osteoporosis	B-HISTORY
,	O
hypothyroidism	B-HISTORY
,	O
allergic	B-HISTORY
rhinitis	I-HISTORY
and	O
kidney	B-HISTORY
stones	I-HISTORY
.	O
Have	O
you	O
noticed	O
any	O
changes	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
concerns	O
regarding	O
these	O
issues	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
fever	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
chills	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
cough	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
congestion	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
chest	B-SYMPTOM
pain	O
,	O
chest	B-SYMPTOM
pressure	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
for	O
our	O
records	B-OTHER
,	O
how	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
and	O
what	O
race	O
do	O
you	O
identify	O
yourself	O
as	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
seventy	O
six	O
years	O
old	O
and	O
identify	O
as	O
a	O
white	O
female	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
'	O
re	O
you	O
feeling	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Terrible	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
having	O
the	O
worst	O
headache	B-SYMPTOM
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
so	O
sorry	O
.	O
Well	O
you	O
are	O
only	O
twenty	O
five	O
,	O
so	O
let	O
'	O
s	O
hope	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
worst	O
.	O
Let	O
'	O
s	O
see	O
how	O
we	O
can	O
best	O
help	O
you	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
it	O
start	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Around	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Um	O
no	O
yesterday	O
.	O
July	O
thirty	O
first	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
July	O
thirty	O
first	O
O	O
eight	O
.	O
Got	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
come	O
on	O
suddenly	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
having	O
any	O
symptoms	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
blurry	B-SYMPTOM
vision	O
,	O
light	B-SYMPTOM
sensitivity	O
,	O
dizziness	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
lightheadedness	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
or	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
having	O
blurry	B-SYMPTOM
vision	O
and	O
lightheadedness	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
I	O
also	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
seem	O
to	O
write	O
well	O
.	O
It	O
looks	O
so	O
messy	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
naturally	O
right	O
handed	O
but	O
my	O
writing	O
looks	O
like	O
I	O
am	O
trying	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
would	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
lightheadedness	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Like	O
there	O
are	O
blind	O
spots	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
How	O
about	O
any	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Um	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
my	O
face	B-SYMPTOM
is	O
pretty	O
swollen	O
though	O
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
headache	B-SYMPTOM
but	O
it	O
started	O
around	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Here	B-LOCATION
in	O
the	O
E	B-ORGANIZATION
R	I-ORGANIZATION
,	O
we	O
'	O
ll	O
do	O
a	O
thorough	O
exam	B-ACTION
and	O
eval	B-ACTION
to	O
make	O
sure	O
nothing	O
serious	O
is	O
going	O
on	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
'	O
re	O
waiting	O
for	O
your	O
C	B-ACTION
T	I-ACTION
results	I-ACTION
,	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
going	O
to	O
order	O
a	O
migraine	B-HISTORY
cocktail	I-HISTORY
and	O
some	O
Morphine	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
.	O
Will	O
the	O
nurse	B-PERSON
be	O
in	B-LOCATION
soon	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
'	O
ll	O
be	O
right	O
in	B-LOCATION
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
order	O
is	O
placed	O
.	O
It	O
shouldn	O
'	O
t	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
takes	O
longer	O
,	O
then	O
please	O
ring	O
the	O
call	O
bell	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
,	O
miss	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
for	O
your	O
visit	B-ACTION
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
warts	B-SYMPTOM
on	O
my	O
back	B-SYMPTOM
end	O
where	O
the	O
poop	B-SYMPTOM
comes	O
out	B-LOCATION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
start	O
noticing	O
them	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
think	O
like	O
three	O
to	O
four	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
discomfort	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
itches	B-SYMPTOM
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
haven	O
'	O
t	O
felt	O
any	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
yet	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
normal	O
for	O
a	O
twenty	O
two	O
year	O
old	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ll	O
have	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
'	O
ll	O
be	O
fine	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
symptoms	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
aware	O
of	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Just	O
the	O
warts	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
itchiness	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
taking	O
any	O
over	B-HISTORY
the	I-HISTORY
counter	I-HISTORY
medicines	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
ones	O
which	O
were	O
prescribed	B-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
alternative	B-HISTORY
medicine	I-HISTORY
,	O
naturopathy	B-HISTORY
or	O
anything	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
whatever	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
this	O
prescription	B-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
so	O
you	O
were	O
prescribed	B-ACTION
Salmeterol	B-HISTORY
inhaler	I-HISTORY
-	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
On	O
as	O
needed	O
basis	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
is	O
Fluticasone	B-HISTORY
inhaler	I-HISTORY
,	O
which	O
is	O
-	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Which	O
is	O
a	O
nasal	B-ACTION
inhaler	I-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Right	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
burned	B-HISTORY
my	I-HISTORY
hand	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
.	O
Wow	O
!	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
it	O
only	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
arm	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
'	O
s	O
your	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
since	O
you	O
started	O
using	O
your	O
inhaler	B-ACTION
again	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Much	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
why	O
I	O
didn	O
'	O
t	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
everywhere	B-LOCATION
I	O
went	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
important	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
especially	O
during	O
times	O
where	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
exercising	B-ACTION
or	O
walking	B-ACTION
more	O
than	O
usual	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
learned	O
my	O
lesson	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Besides	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
,	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
other	O
medical	B-HISTORY
problems	I-HISTORY
?	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
quit	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
currently	O
pregnant	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
complications	O
with	O
the	O
birth	B-HISTORY
of	O
your	O
daughter	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
actually	O
had	O
a	O
C	B-ACTION
section	I-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
surgeries	B-ACTION
in	O
the	O
past	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
appendix	B-SYMPTOM
out	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
other	O
issues	O
,	O
like	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	O
pressure	O
or	O
heart	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
problems	O
with	O
the	O
lungs	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
thyroid	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
kidney	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
or	O
bladder	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
did	O
you	O
hurt	B-SYMPTOM
your	O
lower	O
back	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
now	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
car	B-HISTORY
crash	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
treatments	B-ACTION
were	O
recommended	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
They	O
didn	O
'	O
t	O
recommend	O
P	B-ACTION
T	I-ACTION
,	O
and	O
I	O
didn	O
'	O
t	O
really	O
have	O
any	O
increased	B-SYMPTOM
back	O
pain	O
after	O
the	O
accident	B-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
know	O
drug	B-HISTORY
allergies	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
there	B-LOCATION
,	O
sir	O
!	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
good	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
start	O
with	O
your	O
family	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
today	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
their	O
medical	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
mother	O
and	O
father	O
both	O
had	O
heart	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
.	O
Well	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
had	O
complication	O
from	O
her	O
heart	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
and	O
that	O
is	O
how	O
she	O
passed	B-HISTORY
.	O
My	O
father	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
his	O
forty	O
'	O
s	O
when	O
he	O
died	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sorry	O
the	O
hear	O
that	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
brothers	O
,	O
one	O
whom	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
speak	O
to	O
very	O
much	O
anymore	O
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
health	O
problems	O
.	O
My	O
other	O
brother	O
is	O
healthy	O
with	O
no	O
issues	O
.	O
Both	O
my	O
uncles	O
on	O
my	O
mother	O
'	O
s	O
side	B-LOCATION
had	O
polio	B-HISTORY
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Tell	O
me	O
more	O
about	O
your	O
uncles	O
with	O
polio	B-HISTORY
.	O
They	O
both	O
had	O
polio	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
to	O
wear	B-ACTION
crutches	I-ACTION
due	O
to	O
how	O
bad	O
his	O
leg	B-SYMPTOM
deformans	O
were	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
leg	B-SYMPTOM
deformities	O
in	O
only	O
one	B-SYMPTOM
leg	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
fairly	O
certain	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
polio	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
family	O
member	O
with	O
neurological	B-HISTORY
conditions	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
None	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
children	B-PERSON
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
child	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
your	O
child	O
healthy	O
and	O
well	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
about	O
any	O
diseases	B-HISTORY
that	O
run	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
has	O
a	O
prostate	B-HISTORY
cancer	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
brother	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
father	O
had	O
brain	B-HISTORY
cancer	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
dad	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Then	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
heart	B-SYMPTOM
related	O
issues	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
both	O
have	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
it	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
A	B-ORGANIZATION
B	I-ORGANIZATION
C	I-ORGANIZATION
D	I-ORGANIZATION
General	I-ORGANIZATION
Hospital	I-ORGANIZATION
.	O
Before	O
we	O
begin	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
need	O
to	O
confirm	O
some	O
background	O
information	O
on	O
you	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Absolutely	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
no	O
problem	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
First	O
,	O
how	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
nineteen	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
chart	O
says	O
you	O
identify	O
as	O
Caucasian	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
correct	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
correct	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
what	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
problem	O
today	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
had	O
this	O
bunion	B-SYMPTOM
on	O
my	O
foot	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
this	O
bunion	B-SYMPTOM
been	O
present	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
At	O
this	O
point	O
,	O
um	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
even	O
remember	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
other	O
conditions	B-HISTORY
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
aware	O
of	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Actually	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
history	O
of	O
,	O
um	O
,	O
Charcot	B-HISTORY
Marie	I-HISTORY
tooth	I-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
'	O
s	O
good	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
surgery	B-ACTION
to	O
cut	O
this	O
bunion	B-SYMPTOM
off	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
take	O
it	O
anymore	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
hear	O
someone	O
has	O
a	O
birthday	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
how	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
turning	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ll	O
be	O
ninety	O
later	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
You	O
'	O
re	O
here	O
for	O
a	O
follow	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
not	O
very	O
long	O
after	O
your	O
first	O
visit	B-ACTION
.	O
What	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
problem	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
actually	O
,	O
my	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	O
pressure	O
and	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
arm	O
symptoms	O
are	O
basically	O
gone	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
blood	B-ACTION
pressure	I-ACTION
reading	I-ACTION
for	O
today	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
taking	O
the	O
higher	O
dose	O
of	O
Mavik	B-HISTORY
we	O
recommended	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
taking	O
that	O
right	O
now	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
tolerate	O
the	O
higher	O
dose	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
didn	O
'	O
t	O
feel	O
well	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
just	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
dose	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
was	O
one	O
M	O
G	O
per	O
day	O
,	O
correct	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
some	O
white	O
coat	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	O
pressure	O
.	O
Doctors	B-ORGANIZATION
'	I-ORGANIZATION
offices	I-ORGANIZATION
make	O
me	O
nervous	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
does	O
happen	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
try	O
this	O
sample	O
of	O
Tarka	B-HISTORY
,	O
please	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
for	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
taking	O
the	O
Mavik	B-HISTORY
plus	O
verapamil	B-HISTORY
,	O
you	O
can	O
switch	O
over	O
to	O
Tarka	B-HISTORY
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
combined	O
version	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
drugs	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
take	O
these	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
They	O
'	O
re	O
too	O
big	O
.	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Hello	O
doctor	B-PERSON
,	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
her	O
daughter	O
.	O
Just	O
so	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
we	O
check	O
her	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
pressure	O
at	O
home	O
periodically	O
and	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
always	O
similar	O
to	O
that	O
reading	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
,	O
so	O
back	O
to	O
that	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
arm	O
,	O
how	O
is	O
that	O
doing	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
that	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
is	O
basically	O
gone	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
muscle	B-SYMPTOM
problem	O
back	O
in	O
my	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
shoulder	O
blade	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
have	O
x	B-ACTION
rays	I-ACTION
taken	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
tech	B-PERSON
brought	O
me	O
back	B-LOCATION
right	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
images	O
right	O
here	B-LOCATION
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
do	O
they	O
show	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
these	O
x	B-ACTION
rays	I-ACTION
of	I-ACTION
the	I-ACTION
neck	I-ACTION
and	I-ACTION
right	I-ACTION
shoulder	I-ACTION
show	O
some	O
degenerative	B-SYMPTOM
changes	O
,	O
and	O
possibly	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
rotator	B-HISTORY
cuff	I-HISTORY
injury	I-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
there	O
'	O
s	O
an	O
injury	B-HISTORY
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
look	O
right	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
humeral	B-SYMPTOM
head	O
is	O
pretty	O
high	O
in	O
the	O
glenoid	B-SYMPTOM
in	O
the	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
shoulder	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
here	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Then	O
we	O
won	O
'	O
t	O
worry	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
having	O
this	O
stomach	B-SYMPTOM
pain	O
though	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
has	O
this	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
developed	O
and	O
progressed	O
recently	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
improved	O
somewhat	O
with	O
me	O
not	O
taking	O
Aleve	B-HISTORY
anymore	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
medicines	B-HISTORY
are	O
you	O
taking	O
right	O
now	O
,	O
then	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Right	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
just	O
taking	O
Tylenol	B-HISTORY
as	O
needed	O
.	O
That	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
could	O
be	O
acid	B-SYMPTOM
reflux	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
or	O
heartburn	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
take	O
Tums	B-HISTORY
,	O
um	O
,	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Mylanta	B-HISTORY
at	O
night	O
.	O
Oh	O
yeah	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
these	O
sores	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
mouth	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
worn	B-ACTION
dentures	I-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
I	O
couldn	O
'	O
t	O
even	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
many	O
,	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
they	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
,	O
the	O
sores	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
will	O
come	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
'	O
ll	O
heal	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
we	O
'	O
ll	O
keep	O
an	O
eye	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
doctor	B-PERSON
,	O
since	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
been	O
taking	O
the	O
Lexapro	B-HISTORY
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
tremors	B-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
basically	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
whole	I-SYMPTOM
body	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
at	O
least	O
the	O
upper	B-SYMPTOM
body	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
like	O
my	O
torso	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
arms	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
hard	O
to	O
tell	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
tremor	B-SYMPTOM
today	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Lexapro	B-HISTORY
is	O
helping	O
otherwise	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
taking	O
any	O
medications	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
believe	O
in	O
meds	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
really	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
check	O
your	O
list	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
never	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Wow	O
amazing	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
past	O
medical	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
history	O
of	O
peptic	B-HISTORY
ulcer	I-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
and	O
we	O
think	O
she	O
may	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
possible	O
stroke	B-HISTORY
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
double	O
check	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
records	B-OTHER
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Does	O
she	O
see	O
a	O
neurologist	B-PERSON
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Um	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
her	O
son	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
that	O
'	O
d	O
be	O
great	O
.	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
'	O
s	O
also	O
experiencing	O
some	O
memory	B-SYMPTOM
loss	I-SYMPTOM
as	O
of	O
one	O
to	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
it	O
for	O
medical	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
forty	O
four	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
right	O
handed	O
or	O
left	O
handed	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
right	O
handed	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
happened	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
woke	O
up	O
over	O
this	O
numbness	B-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
left	I-SYMPTOM
side	I-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
body	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
July	O
twenty	O
nineth	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
sensation	O
like	O
having	O
pins	O
and	O
needles	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
weakness	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
change	O
in	O
your	O
visual	B-HISTORY
or	I-HISTORY
mental	I-HISTORY
status	I-HISTORY
?	O
Were	O
you	O
able	B-SYMPTOM
to	I-SYMPTOM
walk	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
was	O
able	B-SYMPTOM
to	I-SYMPTOM
walk	I-SYMPTOM
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
weakness	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
any	O
other	O
thing	O
you	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
start	O
noticing	O
these	O
symptoms	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
around	O
Independence	O
Day	O
.	O
It	O
all	O
started	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
that	O
my	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
hand	I-SYMPTOM
is	I-SYMPTOM
very	I-SYMPTOM
clumsy	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
kind	O
of	O
stiff	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Then	O
I	O
noticed	O
leaning	B-SYMPTOM
towards	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
right	I-SYMPTOM
when	O
walking	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
strange	O
.	O
Happened	O
around	O
July	O
seventh	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
recently	O
have	O
any	O
cold	B-SYMPTOM
or	I-SYMPTOM
flu	I-SYMPTOM
like	I-SYMPTOM
symptoms	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Were	O
diagnosed	O
with	O
a	O
thing	O
called	O
multiple	B-HISTORY
sclerosis	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
have	O
a	O
feeling	O
where	O
you	O
felt	O
like	O
there	O
'	O
s	O
an	O
electric	O
is	O
going	O
up	O
or	O
down	O
your	O
spine	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
any	O
fatigue	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Any	O
frequency	O
in	O
your	O
urination	B-HISTORY
?	O
Any	O
urgency	O
in	O
that	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
heart	B-ACTION
surgery	I-ACTION
,	O
right	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
right	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Pacemaker	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
that	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
else	O
?	O
What	O
other	O
surgeries	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
hysterectomy	B-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
young	O
boy	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
twenty	O
nine	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
you	O
got	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
side	I-SYMPTOM
shoulder	I-SYMPTOM
pain	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Is	O
this	O
something	O
new	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
right	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
were	O
you	O
doing	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
picking	O
up	O
a	O
stack	O
of	O
cardboard	O
,	O
then	O
putting	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
twisting	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
.	O
And	O
sometimes	O
I	O
was	O
throwing	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
far	O
you	O
were	O
lifting	O
them	O
or	O
bending	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Around	O
here	O
,	O
till	O
waist	B-SYMPTOM
level	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
pop	O
and	O
since	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
in	O
this	O
area	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
lift	O
heavy	O
items	O
.	O
Basically	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
strength	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
all	O
started	O
from	O
June	O
thirty	O
two	O
thousand	O
and	O
four	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
right	O
.	O
The	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
is	O
in	O
the	O
lateral	B-SYMPTOM
part	I-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
back	I-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
shoulder	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
your	O
arm	B-SYMPTOM
if	O
I	O
may	O
ask	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Motorcycle	B-HISTORY
accident	I-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
start	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
About	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
seem	O
to	O
stomach	O
anything	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
many	O
episodes	O
of	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
have	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
At	O
least	O
four	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
abdominal	B-SYMPTOM
pain	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
fever	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
chill	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
or	O
other	O
symptoms	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Just	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
so	O
terrible	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ll	O
order	O
you	O
some	O
Zofran	B-HISTORY
to	O
help	O
bring	O
the	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
to	O
bay	O
.	O
One	O
moment	O
while	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
order	O
in	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
assistant	B-PERSON
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
helps	O
me	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
your	O
food	B-OTHER
diary	I-OTHER
sheets	I-OTHER
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
please	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
for	O
exercise	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Um	O
,	O
right	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
walk	B-ACTION
around	O
at	O
the	O
mall	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
steps	O
in	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
he	O
currently	O
taking	O
any	O
medication	B-HISTORY
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
No	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
your	O
last	O
visit	B-ACTION
was	O
on	O
July	O
two	O
thousand	O
and	O
seven	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
for	O
that	O
visit	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
was	O
acting	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
felt	O
like	O
I	O
couldn	B-HISTORY
'	I-HISTORY
t	I-HISTORY
breathe	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
history	B-HISTORY
of	I-HISTORY
asthma	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
always	O
get	O
this	O
really	O
bad	B-SYMPTOM
cough	I-SYMPTOM
where	O
I	O
cough	B-SYMPTOM
up	I-SYMPTOM
some	I-SYMPTOM
nasty	I-SYMPTOM
phlegm	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
looking	O
at	O
your	O
report	B-OTHER
and	O
it	O
says	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
history	B-HISTORY
of	I-HISTORY
pneumonia	I-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
any	O
medical	B-HISTORY
traits	I-HISTORY
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
everyone	O
in	O
my	O
family	O
is	O
quite	O
healthy	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
aware	O
of	O
any	O
medical	B-HISTORY
problems	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
sexually	B-HISTORY
active	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
my	O
boyfriend	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
take	B-HISTORY
any	I-HISTORY
drugs	I-HISTORY
or	O
alcohol	B-HISTORY
or	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
past	O
medical	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Um	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
times	O
where	O
I	O
noticed	O
my	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
was	I-SYMPTOM
high	I-SYMPTOM
but	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
improved	O
as	O
of	O
late	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
When	O
did	O
these	O
episodes	O
occur	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
follow	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
with	O
your	O
previous	B-PERSON
doctor	B-PERSON
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
my	O
old	B-PERSON
doctor	B-PERSON
knows	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
then	O
.	O
Let	O
'	O
s	O
see	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
checking	O
your	O
own	O
blood	B-HISTORY
pressure	I-HISTORY
as	O
a	O
result	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
not	O
really	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
your	O
blood	B-HISTORY
pressure	I-HISTORY
was	O
normal	O
today	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
sign	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hm	O
any	O
allergies	B-HISTORY
to	I-HISTORY
medications	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
None	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
it	O
looks	O
like	O
you	O
have	O
gained	O
about	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
since	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
Any	O
new	O
diet	B-OTHER
changes	O
or	O
stressors	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
job	O
last	O
January	O
and	O
it	O
took	O
a	O
pretty	O
big	O
toll	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
.	O
How	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
coping	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
doing	O
better	O
now	O
but	O
I	O
need	O
to	O
watch	O
what	O
I	O
eat	O
.	O
I	O
tend	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
lot	O
more	O
when	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
stressed	O
.	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
something	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
working	O
on	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
allergic	B-HISTORY
to	O
anything	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
allergic	B-HISTORY
to	I-HISTORY
Penicillin	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
other	O
drugs	B-HISTORY
that	O
you	O
could	O
be	O
allergic	B-HISTORY
to	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
brought	O
them	B-PERSON
in	O
today	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Poor	B-SYMPTOM
renal	I-SYMPTOM
sufficiency	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
possibly	O
due	O
to	O
dehydration	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
diabetic	B-SYMPTOM
nephropathy	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
She	O
also	O
has	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
and	O
low	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
sugar	I-SYMPTOM
as	O
a	O
result	O
of	O
missing	O
meals	B-OTHER
regularly	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Doc	B-PERSON
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
diagnose	B-HISTORY
me	O
as	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
We	O
are	O
looking	O
at	O
blood	B-HISTORY
born	I-HISTORY
pathogen	I-HISTORY
exposure	I-HISTORY
secondary	O
to	O
needlestick	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
thinking	O
around	O
contamination	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
car	B-HISTORY
crash	I-HISTORY
,	O
correct	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Correct	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
head	B-HISTORY
on	I-HISTORY
collision	I-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
allergies	B-HISTORY
I	O
should	O
know	O
about	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
,	O
no	O
allergies	B-HISTORY
for	O
me	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
sir	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
first	O
start	O
by	O
asking	O
your	O
age	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
twenty	O
four	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
what	O
brought	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
How	O
can	O
I	O
help	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
for	O
fishing	O
this	O
weekend	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
some	O
poison	B-OTHER
ivy	I-OTHER
and	O
I	O
have	O
these	O
rashes	B-SYMPTOM
all	I-SYMPTOM
over	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
chest	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
legs	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
arms	B-SYMPTOM
and	I-SYMPTOM
also	I-SYMPTOM
some	I-SYMPTOM
are	I-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
back	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
You	O
seem	O
so	O
confident	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
poison	B-OTHER
ivy	I-OTHER
has	O
it	O
happened	O
before	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
happened	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
It	O
usually	O
takes	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
.	O
Last	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
Blackman	I-PERSON
gave	O
me	O
a	O
steroid	B-HISTORY
injection	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
check	O
my	O
records	B-OTHER
.	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
eighty	O
milligrams	O
of	O
depomedrol	B-HISTORY
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
last	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
injection	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
worked	O
fine	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
take	O
us	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
medicine	B-HISTORY
or	O
anything	O
else	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
took	O
over	B-HISTORY
the	I-HISTORY
counter	I-HISTORY
Benadryl	I-HISTORY
.	O
Also	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
applying	O
cortisone	B-HISTORY
cream	I-HISTORY
on	O
the	O
rashes	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
they	O
help	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
improvement	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
weekend	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
worst	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
worries	O
,	O
let	O
'	O
s	O
set	O
you	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
injection	B-ACTION
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
You	O
had	O
mentioned	O
that	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
runs	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
.	O
What	O
type	O
of	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Skin	B-HISTORY
cancer	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
other	O
health	B-SYMPTOM
problems	I-SYMPTOM
in	O
the	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
High	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
,	O
what	O
brings	O
you	O
here	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
feel	O
this	O
lump	B-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
upper	I-SYMPTOM
side	I-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
breast	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Both	B-LOCATION
sides	I-LOCATION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
on	O
the	O
left	B-LOCATION
side	I-LOCATION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
feel	O
it	O
deep	B-LOCATION
inside	I-LOCATION
or	O
on	O
the	O
outer	B-LOCATION
side	I-LOCATION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Only	O
on	O
the	O
outer	B-LOCATION
side	I-LOCATION
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
new	O
to	O
the	O
clinic	B-ORGANIZATION
.	O
Welcome	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
new	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Arizona	B-LOCATION
for	O
the	O
last	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
from	O
Maine	B-LOCATION
.	O
That	O
is	O
where	O
I	O
grow	O
up	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
still	O
lives	O
there	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
line	O
of	O
work	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
homemaker	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
clean	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
while	O
back	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
children	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
children	O
but	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
still	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
My	O
oldest	O
son	O
passed	O
away	O
from	O
ulcerative	B-SYMPTOM
colitis	I-SYMPTOM
complications	I-SYMPTOM
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
!	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
You	O
okay	O
there	B-LOCATION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Uh	O
yeah	O
,	O
sorry	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
just	O
trying	O
to	O
adjust	O
the	O
stretcher	B-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Want	O
some	O
help	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
how	O
'	O
re	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Fine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
weird	O
lump	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
chest	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
notice	O
it	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
there	B-LOCATION
for	O
a	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
d	O
say	O
almost	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
anyone	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
until	O
now	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
it	O
causing	O
you	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
And	O
has	O
it	O
changed	O
in	O
size	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Not	O
really	O
.	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
just	O
noticeable	O
when	O
I	O
run	O
my	O
fingers	B-SYMPTOM
over	O
it	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
spotted	O
any	O
swelling	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
redness	B-SYMPTOM
to	O
the	O
area	B-LOCATION
?	O
Any	O
drainage	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
Okay	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
'	O
ll	O
have	O
you	O
walk	O
down	O
the	O
hall	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
Xray	B-ACTION
so	O
we	O
can	O
see	O
what	O
'	O
s	O
going	O
on	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
are	O
here	O
for	O
follow	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
today	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
will	O
ask	O
you	O
some	O
regular	O
questions	O
,	O
okay	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
urination	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
fever	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
chills	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
noticed	O
any	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
while	O
urinating	B-HISTORY
?	O
Any	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
your	I-SYMPTOM
urine	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
leak	B-HISTORY
,	O
especially	O
when	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
changing	O
my	O
positions	O
like	O
from	O
sitting	O
to	O
standing	O
so	O
I	O
do	O
feel	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
involuntary	B-HISTORY
urination	I-HISTORY
.	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
urge	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
loading	O
data	O
in	O
like	O
every	O
one	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
especially	O
when	O
I	O
take	O
that	O
Lasix	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Does	O
it	O
taper	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
or	O
night	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
tapers	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
And	O
by	O
the	O
night	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
do	O
not	O
feel	O
anything	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
leakage	B-HISTORY
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
apply	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
force	O
to	O
urinate	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
this	O
stream	O
?	O
Is	O
it	O
good	O
or	O
less	O
?	O
Are	O
you	O
emptying	O
well	O
?	O
And	O
what	O
about	O
the	O
bowel	B-HISTORY
movement	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
The	O
stream	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
feel	O
like	O
all	O
is	O
out	O
in	O
one	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
bowel	B-SYMPTOM
issues	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
using	O
my	O
vaginal	B-HISTORY
cream	I-HISTORY
.	O
Sometimes	O
I	O
feel	O
difficulty	O
in	O
doing	O
so	O
because	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
still	O
something	O
coming	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
vagina	O
and	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
afraid	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
prolapse	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Don	O
'	O
t	O
worry	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
lost	O
weight	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
haven	O
'	O
t	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
ask	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
anything	O
like	O
fever	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
as	O
we	O
discussed	O
you	O
have	O
problem	B-SYMPTOM
talking	I-SYMPTOM
and	I-SYMPTOM
comprehending	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
you	O
get	O
urine	B-HISTORY
infections	I-HISTORY
too	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
as	O
discussed	O
,	O
your	O
drainage	B-HISTORY
is	O
similar	O
to	O
past	O
episodes	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
such	O
infection	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
use	O
tobacco	B-HISTORY
products	I-HISTORY
?	O
Cigarettes	B-HISTORY
,	O
chewing	B-HISTORY
tobacco	I-HISTORY
or	O
vaping	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
a	O
pack	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
quit	O
that	O
awful	O
habit	O
in	O
nineteen	O
eighty	O
five	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
work	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
retired	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Wonderful	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
husband	O
retired	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
are	O
.	O
I	O
cannot	O
imagine	O
working	O
a	O
full	O
time	O
job	O
at	O
seventy	O
six	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
there	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
turned	O
eighty	O
-	O
eight	O
yesterday	O
,	O
happy	O
birthday	O
!	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
!	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
you	O
are	O
referred	O
by	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
X	I-PERSON
,	O
he	O
is	O
your	O
primary	O
physician	B-PERSON
,	O
right	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Correct	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
seeing	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
Y	I-PERSON
for	O
my	O
leukemia	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hm	O
he	O
mentioned	O
that	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
chronic	B-HISTORY
lymphocytic	I-HISTORY
leukemia	I-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
you	O
are	O
also	O
seeing	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
Z	I-PERSON
for	O
your	O
heart	B-SYMPTOM
related	I-SYMPTOM
problems	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
is	O
correct	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
is	O
happening	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
For	O
the	O
past	O
one	O
week	O
I	O
am	O
having	O
this	O
increased	B-SYMPTOM
shortness	I-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
breath	I-SYMPTOM
and	O
having	O
difficulty	B-SYMPTOM
breathing	I-SYMPTOM
from	O
past	O
few	O
nights	O
while	O
sleeping	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
having	O
difficulty	B-SYMPTOM
catching	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
breath	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
having	O
wheezing	B-SYMPTOM
since	O
morning	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Let	O
me	O
examine	O
you	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
come	O
forward	O
and	O
sit	O
-	O
up	O
here	B-LOCATION
?	O
Any	O
chest	B-SYMPTOM
discomfort	I-SYMPTOM
or	O
acute	B-HISTORY
chest	I-HISTORY
pain	I-HISTORY
or	O
anything	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
?	O
Any	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
left	I-SYMPTOM
arm	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
dizziness	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
feeling	O
like	O
fainting	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
light	B-SYMPTOM
headedness	I-SYMPTOM
or	O
losing	O
control	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
sign	O
of	O
cardiovascular	B-HISTORY
accident	I-HISTORY
or	O
heart	B-HISTORY
attack	I-HISTORY
,	O
so	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
that	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
have	O
mild	B-HISTORY
peripheral	I-HISTORY
edema	I-HISTORY
.	O
We	O
need	O
to	O
treat	B-ACTION
that	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Ready	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
just	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
wait	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
understand	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Bye	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
See	O
you	O
soon	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
today	O
?	O
Can	O
you	O
confirm	O
your	O
age	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Fifty	O
eight	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
my	O
balance	B-SYMPTOM
is	I-SYMPTOM
off	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
and	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
been	O
feeling	O
tired	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
weak	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
experiencing	O
this	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
going	O
on	O
for	O
six	O
to	O
eight	O
weeks	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
other	O
symptoms	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
haven	O
'	O
t	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
related	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
pneumonia	B-HISTORY
ten	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
all	O
started	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Interesting	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
medication	B-HISTORY
for	O
that	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
pronounce	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Let	O
me	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
took	O
a	O
full	O
course	O
of	O
amoxicillin	B-HISTORY
,	O
right	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
right	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
feel	O
after	O
you	O
finished	O
the	O
antibiotics	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Terrible	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
like	O
I	O
couldn	O
'	O
t	O
control	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
My	O
balance	B-SYMPTOM
got	I-SYMPTOM
even	I-SYMPTOM
worse	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
even	O
more	O
tired	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
weak	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
wow	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
why	O
your	O
balance	B-SYMPTOM
and	I-SYMPTOM
coordination	I-SYMPTOM
worsened	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
did	O
fall	B-HISTORY
recently	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
for	O
a	O
fact	O
my	O
balance	B-SYMPTOM
was	I-SYMPTOM
off	I-SYMPTOM
before	O
my	O
fall	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
high	O
were	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
fell	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
five	O
feet	O
high	O
when	O
I	O
fell	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
fall	B-HISTORY
on	O
your	O
back	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
fell	B-HISTORY
on	O
my	O
feet	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Just	O
kidding	O
,	O
I	O
fell	B-HISTORY
on	O
my	O
back	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Funny	O
.	O
Did	O
anything	O
hurt	B-SYMPTOM
after	O
your	O
fall	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Not	O
really	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
been	O
having	O
some	O
back	B-SYMPTOM
pain	I-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
lower	I-SYMPTOM
and	I-SYMPTOM
mid	I-SYMPTOM
back	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
always	O
have	O
that	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
haven	O
'	O
t	O
.	O
It	O
comes	O
and	O
goes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
done	O
anything	O
to	O
treat	B-ACTION
it	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
started	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
chiropractor	B-PERSON
like	O
five	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
adjusts	O
my	O
neck	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
lower	B-SYMPTOM
back	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
start	O
having	O
problems	B-SYMPTOM
with	I-SYMPTOM
your	I-SYMPTOM
balance	I-SYMPTOM
after	O
this	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
still	O
having	O
problems	O
with	O
that	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chiropractor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
it	O
wasn	O
'	O
t	O
the	O
result	O
of	O
the	O
adjustments	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
anything	O
else	O
that	O
may	O
have	O
caused	O
it	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
this	O
other	O
medicine	B-HISTORY
for	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
remember	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
medication	B-HISTORY
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
it	O
on	O
another	O
paper	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
you	O
took	O
Cipro	B-HISTORY
.	O
This	O
is	O
usually	O
used	O
to	O
treat	B-ACTION
a	O
U	B-HISTORY
T	I-HISTORY
I	I-HISTORY
.	O
Were	O
you	O
aware	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
U	B-HISTORY
T	I-HISTORY
I	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
yeah	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
doctor	B-PERSON
to	O
get	O
some	O
medication	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
more	O
question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
trouble	B-SYMPTOM
controlling	I-SYMPTOM
your	I-SYMPTOM
bowel	I-SYMPTOM
movements	I-SYMPTOM
or	O
attempting	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
bathroom	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
bathroom	O
whenever	O
I	O
want	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
illnesses	B-HISTORY
in	O
the	O
past	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Anything	O
that	O
is	O
worth	O
mentioning	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
My	O
nurse	B-PERSON
tells	O
me	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
twenty	O
eight	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
correct	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
morning	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
correct	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
what	O
happened	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
punched	O
a	O
wall	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Which	O
hand	B-SYMPTOM
is	O
it	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
my	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
hand	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
dominant	O
hand	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Unfortunately	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Where	O
does	O
it	O
hurt	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Um	O
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
right	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
outside	B-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
hand	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
treatments	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
E	B-ORGANIZATION
D	I-ORGANIZATION
,	O
and	O
they	O
pushed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
joints	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
hand	I-SYMPTOM
back	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
splint	B-ACTION
,	O
so	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
been	O
wearing	O
that	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
is	O
your	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Compared	O
to	O
when	O
it	O
started	O
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
much	O
better	O
today	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
would	O
you	O
describe	O
your	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Today	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
d	O
say	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
minimal	B-SYMPTOM
pain	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
numbness	B-SYMPTOM
or	O
tingling	B-SYMPTOM
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
thankfully	O
not	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
there	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
good	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
colleague	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
Mason	I-PERSON
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
assisting	O
me	O
today	O
and	O
taking	O
down	O
notes	O
.	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
there	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
it	O
okay	O
with	O
you	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
join	O
us	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
,	O
no	O
problem	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
Mason	I-PERSON
can	O
you	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Patient	B-PERSON
looks	O
well	O
developed	O
and	O
well	O
nourished	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
alert	O
with	O
not	O
acute	B-HISTORY
distress	I-HISTORY
.	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Got	O
it	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Patient	B-PERSON
had	O
a	O
head	B-HISTORY
injury	I-HISTORY
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
fully	B-HISTORY
conscious	I-HISTORY
.	O
G	B-HISTORY
C	I-HISTORY
S	I-HISTORY
is	O
fifty	O
and	O
nontoxic	B-HISTORY
.	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Anyone	O
sick	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
anyone	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
disorders	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
you	O
worry	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
patient	B-PERSON
do	O
on	O
the	O
activity	B-ACTION
test	I-ACTION
?	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Patient	B-PERSON
was	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
continue	B-ACTION
with	I-ACTION
his	I-ACTION
normal	I-ACTION
activities	I-ACTION
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
feeling	O
fine	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
old	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
he	O
were	O
first	O
evaluated	B-ACTION
in	O
the	O
other	O
hospital	B-ORGANIZATION
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
seven	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Which	O
hospital	B-ORGANIZATION
was	O
that	O
again	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
U	B-ORGANIZATION
I	I-ORGANIZATION
H	I-ORGANIZATION
C	I-ORGANIZATION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
what	O
exactly	O
happened	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
doing	O
all	O
good	O
like	O
seven	O
months	O
before	O
his	O
evaluation	B-ACTION
,	O
then	O
he	O
started	O
having	O
some	O
dizzy	B-SYMPTOM
spells	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
which	O
like	O
stayed	O
for	O
several	O
seconds	O
to	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
regular	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
continue	B-ACTION
his	I-ACTION
activity	I-ACTION
immediately	O
after	O
these	O
dizzy	B-SYMPTOM
spells	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
the	O
intensity	O
change	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Oh	O
yes	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
these	O
spells	O
,	O
they	O
became	O
more	O
frequent	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
now	O
for	O
longer	O
periods	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
evaluation	B-ACTION
,	O
they	O
were	O
like	O
two	O
to	O
three	O
times	O
per	O
day	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
duration	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
They	O
lasted	O
for	O
like	O
two	O
to	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
associated	B-HISTORY
disorder	I-HISTORY
or	O
anything	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
around	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
his	O
evaluation	B-ACTION
his	O
hands	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
they	O
started	O
becoming	O
stressed	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
like	O
stiffer	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
felt	O
tighter	B-SYMPTOM
during	O
these	O
spells	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
He	O
also	O
felt	O
very	B-SYMPTOM
weak	I-SYMPTOM
and	O
tired	B-SYMPTOM
after	O
these	O
episodes	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
major	O
illnesses	B-HISTORY
in	O
the	O
family	O
like	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
or	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
B	I-SYMPTOM
P	O
?	B-SYMPTOM
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
nothing	O
.	O
No	O
major	O
illnesses	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
morning	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
morning	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
just	O
need	O
some	O
background	O
information	O
before	O
we	O
begin	O
today	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
ever	O
had	O
surgery	B-ACTION
,	O
sir	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
actually	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
knee	B-SYMPTOM
,	O
a	O
nose	B-ACTION
job	I-ACTION
,	O
and	O
,	O
um	O
,	O
carotid	B-ACTION
sinus	I-ACTION
surgery	I-ACTION
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
still	O
working	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
retired	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
U	O
S	O
postal	O
service	O
as	O
an	O
electronic	O
technician	O
but	O
took	O
retirement	O
one	O
year	O
earlier	O
due	O
to	O
my	O
disability	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Ah	O
okay	O
.	O
And	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
stay	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
in	O
our	O
apartment	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
alcohol	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
use	O
to	O
drink	O
occasionally	O
,	O
that	O
too	O
very	O
rare	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
my	O
symptoms	O
stated	O
I	O
stopped	O
completely	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
use	O
of	O
recreational	B-HISTORY
or	I-HISTORY
illegal	I-HISTORY
drugs	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
travel	O
anywhere	O
recently	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
really	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
traveled	O
anywhere	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
good	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
,	O
thanks	O
for	O
asking	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
colleague	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
White	I-PERSON
,	O
and	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
taking	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
okay	O
if	O
she	O
joins	O
us	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
sure	O
,	O
no	O
problem	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
White	I-PERSON
,	O
nice	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nice	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
breathe	B-HISTORY
in	I-HISTORY
and	I-HISTORY
out	I-HISTORY
for	O
me	O
?	O
Deep	B-HISTORY
breaths	I-HISTORY
please	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
breath	B-HISTORY
sounds	I-HISTORY
are	I-HISTORY
clear	I-HISTORY
.	O
Lung	B-HISTORY
function	I-HISTORY
looks	I-HISTORY
good	I-HISTORY
.	O
Symmetrical	B-SYMPTOM
rise	I-SYMPTOM
and	I-SYMPTOM
fall	I-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
chest	I-SYMPTOM
as	O
patient	B-PERSON
breathes	B-HISTORY
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
palpate	B-ACTION
your	I-ACTION
chest	I-ACTION
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
just	O
a	O
routine	B-ACTION
exam	I-ACTION
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
White	I-PERSON
can	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
no	O
egophony	B-HISTORY
or	O
tactile	B-HISTORY
fremitus	I-HISTORY
.	O
Guest_clinician	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
board	O
and	O
care	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
nice	O
small	O
care	O
home	O
with	O
some	O
very	O
nice	O
and	O
supportive	O
people	B-PERSON
.	O
It	O
is	O
just	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Safeway	B-LOCATION
on	O
Village	B-LOCATION
Drive	I-LOCATION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Nice	O
.	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
you	O
love	O
living	O
there	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
very	O
relaxed	O
there	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
consume	O
alcohol	B-HISTORY
in	O
any	O
way	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
Sir	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
tobacco	B-HISTORY
consumption	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
try	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
illicit	B-HISTORY
drugs	I-HISTORY
?	O
Any	O
I	B-HISTORY
V	I-HISTORY
drugs	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
kept	O
myself	O
away	O
from	O
all	O
those	O
things	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
surgeries	B-ACTION
in	O
the	O
past	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Actually	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
gallbladder	B-SYMPTOM
removed	O
in	O
nineteen	O
ninety	O
two	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
any	O
other	O
surgeries	B-ACTION
?	O
Think	O
back	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
yeah	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
appendix	B-SYMPTOM
out	O
in	O
nineteen	O
eighty	O
eight	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
are	O
feeling	O
now	O
after	O
the	O
treatment	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
feeling	O
pretty	O
fair	O
,	O
improving	O
slowly	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Sir	O
?	O
Can	O
you	O
hear	O
me	O
?	O
Are	O
you	O
Mister	O
Smith	O
'	O
s	O
wife	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
how	O
your	O
husband	O
'	O
s	O
condition	O
has	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
point	O
?	O
His	O
level	O
of	O
consciousness	B-HISTORY
is	O
concerning	O
.	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
eighty	O
five	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
entire	O
M	O
G	O
of	O
Xanax	B-HISTORY
.	O
He	O
is	O
only	O
supposed	O
to	O
take	O
point	O
one	O
twenty	O
five	O
M	O
G	O
of	O
Xanax	B-HISTORY
.	O
That	O
is	O
why	O
he	O
is	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
your	O
husband	O
was	O
admitted	B-ACTION
to	O
the	O
emergency	B-ORGANIZATION
room	I-ORGANIZATION
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
these	O
injuries	B-HISTORY
to	I-HISTORY
his	I-HISTORY
face	I-HISTORY
happen	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
fell	B-HISTORY
off	I-HISTORY
his	O
wheelchair	B-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
The	O
Adult	B-ORGANIZATION
Protective	I-ORGANIZATION
Services	I-ORGANIZATION
said	O
they	O
found	O
your	O
husband	O
in	O
the	O
home	O
barley	B-HISTORY
conscious	I-HISTORY
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
All	O
day	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
other	O
medications	B-HISTORY
your	O
husband	O
has	O
taken	O
other	O
than	O
the	O
Xanax	B-HISTORY
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
didn	O
'	O
t	O
take	O
his	O
regular	O
medications	B-HISTORY
for	O
two	O
days	O
.	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
feeling	O
?	O
Is	O
the	O
Wellbutrin	B-HISTORY
keeping	O
your	O
mood	O
stabilized	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
feeling	O
good	O
.	O
The	O
Wellbutrin	B-HISTORY
is	O
working	O
well	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
is	O
important	O
to	O
not	O
consume	O
any	O
alcohol	B-HISTORY
or	O
recreational	B-HISTORY
drugs	I-HISTORY
while	O
taking	O
Wellbutrin	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
drink	O
or	O
do	O
drugs	B-HISTORY
.	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Tell	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
about	O
your	O
family	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
dad	O
and	O
grandpa	O
both	O
had	O
type	B-HISTORY
two	I-HISTORY
diabetes	I-HISTORY
.	O
My	O
son	O
is	O
struggling	O
with	O
type	B-HISTORY
one	I-HISTORY
diabetes	I-HISTORY
at	O
the	O
moment	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
.	O
Does	O
anyone	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
have	O
heart	B-SYMPTOM
problems	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Two	O
of	O
my	O
cousins	O
had	O
breast	B-HISTORY
cancer	I-HISTORY
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
work	O
,	O
miss	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
you	O
see	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
civil	O
engineer	O
.	O
Right	O
now	O
,	O
due	O
to	O
pandemic	B-HISTORY
like	O
everyone	O
else	O
I	O
am	O
working	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
working	O
full	O
time	O
or	O
is	O
your	O
disability	B-HISTORY
affecting	O
that	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
work	O
on	O
half	O
time	O
.	O
This	O
disability	B-HISTORY
does	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
work	O
full	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
physical	B-ACTION
therapy	I-ACTION
quite	O
frequently	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
and	O
I	O
also	O
have	O
a	O
baby	O
who	O
consumes	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
or	O
drink	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
never	O
done	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
familiar	B-HISTORY
diseases	I-HISTORY
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
like	O
B	B-HISTORY
P	I-HISTORY
,	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
sugar	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
my	O
family	O
has	O
anything	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
anxiety	B-HISTORY
attacks	I-HISTORY
lately	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
felt	O
depressed	B-HISTORY
or	O
had	O
any	O
mood	B-SYMPTOM
swing	I-SYMPTOM
problems	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
phobias	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
really	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
history	O
of	O
mental	B-HISTORY
illness	I-HISTORY
or	O
psychological	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
sir	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
today	O
?	O
You	O
still	O
look	O
a	O
little	O
uncomfortable	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Is	O
there	O
still	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
.	O
Still	O
a	O
good	O
amount	O
of	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
pain	B-HISTORY
medication	I-HISTORY
this	O
morning	O
though	O
.	O
Not	O
sure	O
if	O
that	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
is	O
possibly	O
why	O
you	O
are	O
still	O
in	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
How	O
is	O
movement	B-HISTORY
?	O
Can	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
get	O
around	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
happy	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
my	O
daily	O
activities	B-ACTION
.	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
up	O
with	O
minimal	O
assistance	O
and	O
do	O
many	O
activities	B-ACTION
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
gaining	B-HISTORY
muscle	I-HISTORY
from	O
moving	O
around	O
more	O
too	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
is	O
the	O
home	B-ACTION
exercise	I-ACTION
program	I-ACTION
going	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
loving	O
pool	B-ACTION
therapy	I-ACTION
.	O
I	O
really	O
feel	O
like	O
that	O
is	O
helping	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
the	O
home	B-ACTION
exercises	I-ACTION
sometimes	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
back	O
to	O
normal	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
surgeries	B-ACTION
in	O
the	O
past	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
knee	B-ACTION
surgery	I-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Which	O
knee	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Right	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
sexually	B-HISTORY
active	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
many	O
partners	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Just	O
one	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
this	O
a	O
monogamous	O
relationship	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
gender	B-HISTORY
is	O
you	O
partner	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
male	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
together	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
H	B-HISTORY
I	I-HISTORY
V	I-HISTORY
positive	I-HISTORY
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
remember	O
you	O
mentioned	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
one	O
operation	B-ACTION
done	O
in	O
the	O
past	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lymph	B-ACTION
node	I-ACTION
biopsy	I-ACTION
back	O
in	O
September	O
of	O
O	O
three	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
it	O
come	O
back	O
negative	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Fortunately	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
extensive	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
blame	O
my	O
heart	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
It	O
'	O
s	O
caused	O
me	O
the	O
most	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
coronary	B-ACTION
artery	I-ACTION
bypass	I-ACTION
surgery	I-ACTION
in	O
twenty	O
ten	O
along	O
with	O
an	O
angioplasty	B-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
sorry	O
that	O
your	O
heart	B-SYMPTOM
has	O
been	O
giving	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
happy	O
that	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
here	O
with	O
us	O
today	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
right	O
measures	O
to	O
keep	O
yourself	O
healthy	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
had	O
prostate	B-ACTION
biopsies	I-ACTION
in	O
the	O
past	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
biopsies	B-ACTION
done	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Last	O
year	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
they	O
come	O
back	O
negative	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
fortunately	O
.	O
I	O
guess	O
my	O
prostate	B-SYMPTOM
isn	O
'	O
t	O
as	O
troublesome	O
as	O
my	O
heart	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
understand	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
medical	B-HISTORY
problems	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Let	O
'	O
s	O
see	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
,	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
cholesterol	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
and	O
osteoporosis	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
any	O
surgeries	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Several	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Which	O
ones	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
tonsils	B-SYMPTOM
taken	O
out	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
kid	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
had	O
my	O
uterus	B-SYMPTOM
removed	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
ovaries	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
fallopian	B-SYMPTOM
tubes	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
The	O
list	O
goes	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
appendix	B-SYMPTOM
removed	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
parathyroids	B-SYMPTOM
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Despite	O
getting	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
parathyroids	B-SYMPTOM
removed	O
,	O
I	O
still	O
have	O
borderline	B-SYMPTOM
high	I-SYMPTOM
calcium	I-SYMPTOM
levels	I-SYMPTOM
according	O
to	O
my	O
endocrinologist	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Did	O
you	O
experience	O
any	O
complications	O
during	O
or	O
after	O
surgery	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
carpel	B-ACTION
tunnel	I-ACTION
releases	I-ACTION
as	O
well	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
family	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
mother	O
passed	B-HISTORY
away	I-HISTORY
from	O
complications	O
with	O
Huntington	B-HISTORY
Disease	I-HISTORY
.	O
She	O
was	O
diagnosed	B-ACTION
and	O
had	O
been	O
having	O
treatments	O
at	O
U	B-ORGANIZATION
I	I-ORGANIZATION
H	I-ORGANIZATION
C	I-ORGANIZATION
.	O
My	O
grandmother	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
aunts	O
also	O
passed	B-HISTORY
away	I-HISTORY
from	O
Huntington	B-HISTORY
as	O
well	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sorry	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
siblings	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
sister	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
thirty	O
eight	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
metal	B-HISTORY
issues	I-HISTORY
.	O
She	O
has	O
attempted	B-HISTORY
suicide	I-HISTORY
two	O
times	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
close	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Not	O
really	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
married	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
children	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
two	O
adopted	O
kids	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
medical	B-HISTORY
problems	I-HISTORY
on	O
your	O
mom	O
or	O
dad	O
'	O
s	O
side	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
dad	O
has	O
lupus	B-HISTORY
and	O
his	O
brother	O
has	O
Addison	B-HISTORY
'	I-HISTORY
s	I-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
.	O
High	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
also	O
runs	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
your	O
dad	O
being	O
treated	B-ACTION
for	O
lupus	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
follows	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
with	O
his	O
rheumatologist	B-PERSON
pretty	O
regularly	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
a	O
quick	O
exam	B-ACTION
on	O
you	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
exam	B-ACTION
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
just	O
checking	O
for	O
lymph	B-SYMPTOM
nodes	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Whenever	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
infection	B-HISTORY
those	O
guys	O
are	O
the	O
first	O
ones	O
to	O
be	O
noticed	O
with	O
swelling	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
so	O
let	O
'	O
s	O
first	O
check	O
your	O
neck	B-SYMPTOM
area	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
It	O
looks	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
feel	O
any	O
inflamed	B-SYMPTOM
lymph	I-SYMPTOM
node	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Your	O
armpits	B-SYMPTOM
look	O
good	O
too	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
place	O
to	O
check	O
is	O
your	O
groin	B-SYMPTOM
area	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
good	O
.	O
No	O
sign	O
of	O
infection	B-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
are	O
some	O
medications	B-HISTORY
you	O
are	O
on	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
pain	B-HISTORY
pills	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Oxycontin	B-HISTORY
and	O
Vicodin	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
that	O
helps	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
list	O
of	O
your	O
medication	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
All	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
is	O
Risperdal	B-HISTORY
and	O
Invega	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
correct	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
not	O
taking	O
anything	O
else	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
some	O
multivitamins	B-HISTORY
,	O
but	O
do	O
I	O
need	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
.	O
We	O
need	O
to	O
know	O
everything	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
morning	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
good	O
morning	O
,	O
doctor	B-PERSON
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Please	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
about	O
your	O
living	O
situation	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
right	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
kids	O
and	O
my	O
dad	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
here	O
that	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
well	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
more	O
about	O
that	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
use	O
the	O
stairs	O
without	O
holding	O
the	O
rail	O
the	O
entire	O
time	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Holding	O
the	O
rail	O
makes	O
navigating	B-HISTORY
the	O
stairs	O
easier	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
move	B-HISTORY
very	I-HISTORY
slow	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
about	O
a	O
pack	O
to	O
a	O
pack	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
about	O
exercise	B-ACTION
?	O
Do	O
you	O
workout	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
regularly	O
workout	B-ACTION
,	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
never	O
been	O
good	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
physician	B-PERSON
did	O
a	O
blood	B-ACTION
test	I-ACTION
.	O
My	O
potassium	B-SYMPTOM
is	I-SYMPTOM
high	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
He	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
blood	B-OTHER
report	I-OTHER
yet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
waiting	O
for	O
your	O
doctor	B-PERSON
'	B-ORGANIZATION
s	I-ORGANIZATION
office	I-ORGANIZATION
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
only	O
your	O
potassium	B-SYMPTOM
that	O
is	O
elevated	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
what	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
surprise	O
but	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
car	B-HISTORY
accident	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
!	O
He	O
does	O
have	O
multiple	B-HISTORY
trauma	I-HISTORY
due	O
to	O
the	O
accident	B-HISTORY
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
require	O
aftercare	B-ACTION
.	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Yeah	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
family	O
'	O
s	O
living	O
situation	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Um	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
May	O
I	O
assume	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
his	O
biological	O
parents	B-PERSON
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
correct	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
does	O
he	O
have	O
any	O
siblings	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
right	O
now	O
,	O
he	O
'	O
s	O
an	O
only	O
child	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
grade	O
is	O
he	O
in	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
He	O
'	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
grade	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
he	O
doing	O
well	O
in	O
school	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
'	O
s	O
doing	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
what	O
gender	B-HISTORY
do	O
you	O
identify	O
with	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
asking	O
,	O
I	O
identify	O
as	O
a	O
female	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
chronic	B-HISTORY
illnesses	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
examples	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
osteoarthritis	B-HISTORY
,	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
,	O
depression	B-HISTORY
,	O
anything	O
like	O
that	O
ring	O
any	O
bells	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
have	O
anything	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
major	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
conditions	I-HISTORY
that	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
about	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
,	O
like	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
doesn	O
'	O
t	O
have	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
serious	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
there	O
anything	O
you	O
take	O
medicine	B-HISTORY
for	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
allergies	B-HISTORY
and	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
something	O
about	O
your	O
mom	O
and	O
dad	O
?	O
Like	O
any	O
diseases	B-HISTORY
they	O
have	O
had	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Sure	O
,	O
my	O
dad	O
died	B-HISTORY
of	O
heart	B-HISTORY
attack	I-HISTORY
when	O
he	O
was	O
sixty	O
five	O
and	O
my	O
mom	O
died	B-HISTORY
of	O
stroke	B-HISTORY
when	O
she	O
was	O
seventy	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
'	O
s	O
about	O
siblings	O
,	O
miss	O
?	O
Any	O
health	O
issues	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
is	O
healthy	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Does	O
anyone	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
suffer	O
from	O
any	O
health	O
problems	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
one	O
comes	O
to	O
mind	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Tell	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
'	O
s	O
going	O
on	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
is	O
complaining	O
of	O
weakness	B-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
right	I-SYMPTOM
side	I-SYMPTOM
of	I-SYMPTOM
her	I-SYMPTOM
face	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
And	O
I	O
feel	O
the	O
right	B-SYMPTOM
side	I-SYMPTOM
is	I-SYMPTOM
drooping	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
chart	O
here	O
says	O
that	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
eighty	O
three	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
correct	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
doctor	B-PERSON
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
correct	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
had	O
my	O
birthday	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Happy	O
belated	O
birthday	O
!	O
How	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
since	O
your	O
last	O
visit	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
my	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
hasn	O
'	O
t	O
needed	O
phlebotomies	B-HISTORY
for	O
several	O
months	O
now	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
'	O
s	O
great	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
treated	B-ACTION
for	O
polycythemia	B-HISTORY
vera	I-HISTORY
,	O
correct	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
the	O
one	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
also	O
see	O
you	O
'	O
re	O
unassisted	O
today	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
also	O
great	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
independence	O
is	O
nice	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
family	O
history	O
of	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
remember	O
who	O
had	O
what	O
kind	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Still	O
,	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
helpful	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
What	O
about	O
heart	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
too	O
,	O
there	O
'	O
s	O
some	O
history	O
of	O
heart	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
'	O
t	O
remember	O
who	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
are	O
there	O
any	O
major	B-HISTORY
health	I-HISTORY
conditions	I-HISTORY
that	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Anything	O
like	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
,	O
or	O
arthritis	B-HISTORY
,	O
do	O
those	O
sound	O
familiar	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
um	O
,	O
no	O
nothing	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
medical	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
that	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
aware	O
of	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
have	O
type	B-HISTORY
two	I-HISTORY
diabetes	I-HISTORY
.	O
My	O
numbers	O
always	O
come	O
high	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
anything	O
else	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
also	O
have	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
cholesterol	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
feeling	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
just	O
here	O
for	O
my	O
yearly	B-ACTION
physical	I-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
your	O
past	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
is	O
missing	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
'	O
ve	O
had	O
any	O
health	O
related	O
problems	O
before	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Uhm	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
check	O
my	O
notes	O
on	O
my	O
phone	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
this	O
question	O
would	O
pop	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
always	O
forget	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
perfect	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
want	O
to	O
verify	O
the	O
information	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
,	O
nasal	B-HISTORY
inflammation	I-HISTORY
,	O
and	O
some	O
abnormal	B-SYMPTOM
growth	I-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
you	I-SYMPTOM
neck	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
correct	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
If	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
on	O
there	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
usually	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
remember	O
these	O
kinds	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
is	O
usually	O
here	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
knows	O
all	O
about	O
my	O
health	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
'	O
s	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
doing	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
is	O
doing	O
okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
your	O
pregnancy	B-HISTORY
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Thirty	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Was	O
your	O
delivery	B-ACTION
normal	O
or	O
C	B-ACTION
section	I-ACTION
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
C	B-ACTION
section	I-ACTION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
she	O
weigh	B-HISTORY
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
eight	O
pounds	O
and	O
three	O
ounces	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
'	O
s	O
the	O
issue	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
history	O
of	O
seizures	B-HISTORY
.	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
she	O
is	O
having	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
her	I-SYMPTOM
tummy	I-SYMPTOM
and	O
is	O
throwing	B-SYMPTOM
up	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
else	O
did	O
you	O
notice	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
she	O
is	O
having	O
some	O
rashes	B-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
her	I-SYMPTOM
skin	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
There	O
is	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
for	O
sure	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
feels	B-SYMPTOM
bloated	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
She	O
also	O
complains	O
of	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
her	I-SYMPTOM
tummy	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Sometimes	O
she	O
does	O
scratch	O
her	O
mouth	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
We	O
also	O
noticed	O
some	O
swelling	B-SYMPTOM
around	I-SYMPTOM
her	I-SYMPTOM
lips	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
eyes	B-SYMPTOM
and	I-SYMPTOM
face	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
she	O
'	O
s	O
having	O
some	O
food	B-HISTORY
intolerance	I-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
medications	B-HISTORY
are	O
you	O
taking	O
right	O
now	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
taking	O
Advair	B-HISTORY
and	O
Allegra	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
is	O
it	O
helping	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
the	O
Allegra	B-HISTORY
is	O
helping	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
do	O
take	O
them	O
regularly	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
But	O
is	O
it	O
like	O
better	O
than	O
Claritin	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
that	O
'	O
s	O
good	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Shall	O
I	O
continue	O
?	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Anybody	O
sick	O
in	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
one	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
any	O
illnesses	B-HISTORY
that	O
run	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
everyone	O
is	O
healthy	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
again	O
!	O
How	O
has	O
your	O
acne	B-HISTORY
been	O
since	O
you	O
started	O
the	O
spironolactone	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
improving	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
experienced	O
any	O
increased	B-SYMPTOM
thirst	I-SYMPTOM
,	O
mood	B-SYMPTOM
changes	I-SYMPTOM
or	O
unusual	B-SYMPTOM
fatigue	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
think	O
you	O
need	O
any	O
restraints	B-ACTION
as	O
you	O
are	O
doing	O
fine	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
want	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
chair	B-ACTION
and	I-ACTION
bed	I-ACTION
monitor	I-ACTION
since	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
history	O
of	O
multiple	O
falls	B-HISTORY
.	O
They	O
can	O
help	O
detect	O
fall	B-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
want	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
manage	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
!	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
tetanus	B-ACTION
shot	I-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
remember	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
there	O
!	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
good	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Welcome	O
in	O
!	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Lets	O
start	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
social	B-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
tobacco	B-HISTORY
or	O
alcohol	B-HISTORY
user	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
married	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
children	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
married	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
have	O
a	O
two	O
year	O
old	O
son	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
currently	O
see	O
a	O
gynecologist	B-PERSON
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
Bartow	B-LOCATION
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
.	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Tell	O
me	O
about	O
your	O
family	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
family	O
is	O
pretty	O
healthy	O
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
health	O
problems	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Welcome	O
in	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
smoke	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
.	O
Smoking	B-HISTORY
is	O
gross	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
agree	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
drink	O
alcohol	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
drink	O
per	O
day	O
or	O
week	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
When	O
I	O
get	O
off	O
work	O
usually	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	B-OTHER
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
ever	O
have	O
more	O
then	O
one	O
glass	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
The	O
nurse	B-PERSON
applied	O
antibiotic	B-ACTION
ointment	I-ACTION
and	O
a	O
bandage	B-ACTION
to	O
your	O
foot	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Did	O
she	O
go	O
over	O
how	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
bandage	B-ACTION
at	O
home	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
.	O
Before	O
we	O
begin	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
you	O
to	O
confirm	O
some	O
information	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
information	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
About	O
your	O
family	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
certain	O
medical	B-HISTORY
conditions	I-HISTORY
that	O
run	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Nope	O
.	O
My	O
family	O
is	O
very	O
healthy	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
about	O
any	O
breathing	B-SYMPTOM
issues	I-SYMPTOM
or	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Actually	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
history	O
of	O
asthma	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
okay	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
it	O
severe	O
or	O
mild	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
severe	O
but	O
still	O
remarkable	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hm	O
,	O
alright	O
.	O
Anything	O
else	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
struggled	O
with	O
a	O
serious	B-SYMPTOM
acne	I-SYMPTOM
problem	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Got	O
it	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
'	O
s	O
she	O
doing	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
'	O
s	O
had	O
better	O
days	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Aw	O
and	O
why	O
'	O
s	O
that	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
She	O
'	O
s	O
been	O
really	O
congested	B-SYMPTOM
recently	O
.	O
Snorting	B-HISTORY
a	O
lot	O
more	O
,	O
too	O
.	O
She	O
'	O
s	O
onlt	O
eleven	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
odd	O
she	O
snores	B-HISTORY
so	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
allergist	B-PERSON
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
not	O
her	O
allergies	B-HISTORY
so	O
we	O
stopped	O
giving	O
her	O
Allegra	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Does	B-PERSON
she	O
happen	O
to	O
snore	B-HISTORY
at	O
night	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
really	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hm	O
.	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
And	O
while	O
we	O
'	O
re	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
wanted	O
you	O
to	O
check	O
out	O
her	O
toe	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
The	O
right	O
big	B-SYMPTOM
toe	I-SYMPTOM
appears	I-SYMPTOM
a	I-SYMPTOM
bit	I-SYMPTOM
red	I-SYMPTOM
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
skin	B-SYMPTOM
around	I-SYMPTOM
it	I-SYMPTOM
has	I-SYMPTOM
been	I-SYMPTOM
peeling	I-SYMPTOM
for	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Lemme	O
take	O
a	O
look	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
applied	O
anything	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
?	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Why	O
are	O
you	O
holding	O
your	O
face	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Ah	O
!	O
Have	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
tooth	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
how	O
bad	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
awfully	O
bad	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sorry	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
similar	O
symptoms	O
before	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
never	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
other	O
complaints	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
past	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Just	O
some	O
knee	B-SYMPTOM
pain	I-SYMPTOM
issues	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
so	O
chronic	B-HISTORY
knee	I-HISTORY
pain	I-HISTORY
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
about	O
any	O
cancers	B-HISTORY
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
has	O
ovarian	B-HISTORY
cancer	I-HISTORY
,	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
has	O
liver	B-HISTORY
cancer	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sorry	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
is	O
okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
heart	B-HISTORY
conditions	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
My	O
mom	O
and	O
dad	O
both	O
have	O
heart	B-HISTORY
disease	I-HISTORY
.	O
My	O
dad	O
has	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
too	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
problems	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
past	O
.	O
Or	O
what	O
medical	B-HISTORY
issues	I-HISTORY
are	O
currently	O
going	O
on	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
You	O
mean	O
my	O
heart	B-HISTORY
problem	I-HISTORY
and	O
things	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
hypertension	B-HISTORY
and	O
kidney	B-HISTORY
problems	I-HISTORY
since	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
get	O
frequent	O
urinary	B-HISTORY
infections	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Your	O
urine	B-HISTORY
creatinine	I-HISTORY
is	O
normal	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
have	O
severe	B-HISTORY
aortic	I-HISTORY
stenosis	I-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Does	O
anyone	O
else	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
have	O
aneurysm	B-HISTORY
problem	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Well	O
,	O
my	O
grandmother	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
actually	O
passed	B-HISTORY
away	I-HISTORY
due	O
to	O
brain	B-HISTORY
aneurysm	I-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
okay	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
is	O
wrong	O
with	O
your	O
back	B-SYMPTOM
honey	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
,	O
it	O
all	O
started	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
little	B-SYMPTOM
pimple	I-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
the	I-SYMPTOM
buttock	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
I	O
was	O
soaking	O
it	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
hot	O
water	B-OTHER
and	O
stuff	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
improve	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
.	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
twenty	O
four	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
what	O
exactly	O
are	O
you	O
experiencing	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
have	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	B-ORGANIZATION
on	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
an	O
I	B-ACTION
and	O
D	B-ACTION
in	O
E	B-ORGANIZATION
D	I-ORGANIZATION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
the	O
hospitalist	B-ORGANIZATION
service	I-ORGANIZATION
with	O
high	B-SYMPTOM
blood	I-SYMPTOM
sugars	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
My	O
African	O
American	O
father	O
was	O
so	O
scared	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
sugars	B-SYMPTOM
high	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
number	O
?	O
How	O
high	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
positive	O
bacteria	B-HISTORY
or	O
some	O
sort	O
of	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
culture	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
today	O
we	O
are	O
evaluating	O
you	O
for	O
surgery	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
there	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
results	B-OTHER
from	O
your	O
ultrasound	B-ACTION
.	O
You	O
have	O
kidney	B-HISTORY
stones	I-HISTORY
in	O
the	O
ureter	B-SYMPTOM
close	O
to	O
the	O
bladder	B-SYMPTOM
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Oh	O
no	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
This	O
explains	O
the	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
you	O
have	O
been	O
having	O
on	O
your	O
left	B-LOCATION
side	I-LOCATION
.	O
Are	O
you	O
still	O
experiencing	O
nausea	B-SYMPTOM
and	O
vomiting	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
set	O
you	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
consult	B-PERSON
with	O
a	O
consult	B-PERSON
with	O
a	O
surgeon	B-PERSON
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Any	O
known	O
drug	B-HISTORY
allergies	I-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Your	O
daughter	O
had	O
an	O
exposure	O
to	O
the	O
ant	B-HISTORY
bait	I-HISTORY
but	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
sure	O
if	O
she	O
actually	O
ingested	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Poison	B-ORGANIZATION
Control	I-ORGANIZATION
confirmed	O
that	O
even	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
ingest	O
the	O
small	O
amount	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
likely	O
nontoxic	B-HISTORY
.	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
questions	O
?	O
Guest_family	O
:	O
No	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hello	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
am	O
alright	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
for	O
a	O
check	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
since	O
I	O
am	O
feeling	O
kind	O
of	O
dizzy	B-SYMPTOM
lately	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
good	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
this	O
been	O
happening	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
A	O
few	O
months	O
.	O
This	O
happened	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
still	O
dealing	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
family	B-HISTORY
medical	I-HISTORY
history	I-HISTORY
I	O
should	O
know	O
about	O
?	O
Migraines	B-HISTORY
or	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
seems	O
pretty	O
healthy	O
.	O
"	O

Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
anyone	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
whose	O
had	O
cancer	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
so	O
your	O
blood	B-OTHER
report	I-OTHER
is	O
back	O
and	O
the	O
cardiac	B-HISTORY
enzyme	I-HISTORY
we	O
were	O
looking	O
for	O
are	O
negative	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Your	O
blood	B-HISTORY
urea	I-HISTORY
nitrogen	I-HISTORY
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
B	B-HISTORY
U	I-HISTORY
N	I-HISTORY
,	O
is	O
within	O
normal	O
limits	O
and	O
hydrogen	B-HISTORY
is	O
stable	O
.	O
Creatinine	B-HISTORY
is	O
also	O
within	O
the	O
normal	O
range	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Great	O
!	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
on	O
any	O
medications	B-HISTORY
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
taking	O
any	O
medications	B-HISTORY
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Hi	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
been	O
better	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
So	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
here	O
for	O
your	O
follow	B-ACTION
up	I-ACTION
right	O
?	O
Remind	O
me	O
how	O
often	O
are	O
you	O
coming	O
here	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
That	O
'	O
s	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
coming	O
around	O
between	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
it	O
'	O
s	O
every	O
four	O
to	O
eight	O
weeks	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
taking	O
any	O
medicine	B-HISTORY
now	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
wanted	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
record	B-OTHER
.	O
It	O
says	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
off	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
immunosuppression	B-HISTORY
.	O
So	O
,	O
just	O
let	O
me	O
check	O
.	O
It	O
says	O
here	O
that	O
you	O
do	O
have	O
mild	B-HISTORY
chronic	I-HISTORY
G	I-HISTORY
V	I-HISTORY
H	I-HISTORY
D	I-HISTORY
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
bad	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
worried	O
about	O
any	O
therapy	B-ACTION
or	O
anything	O
else	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
that	O
transplant	B-ACTION
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
around	O
four	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
feeling	O
much	O
better	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
have	O
complaints	O
of	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
in	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
stool	I-SYMPTOM
.	O
But	O
after	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
that	O
doctor	B-PERSON
,	O
that	O
gastro	B-PERSON
doctor	B-PERSON
,	O
I	O
feel	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
removed	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
improved	O
a	O
lot	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Okay	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
in	O
my	O
chart	B-OTHER
.	O
You	O
had	O
some	O
rectal	B-SYMPTOM
bleeding	I-SYMPTOM
issues	I-SYMPTOM
because	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
referred	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
gastroenterologist	B-PERSON
.	O
A	O
complete	B-ACTION
endoscopy	I-ACTION
was	O
performed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
upper	B-LOCATION
and	I-LOCATION
the	I-LOCATION
lower	I-LOCATION
side	I-LOCATION
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
ulcers	B-HISTORY
or	O
any	O
other	O
abnormality	B-HISTORY
.	O
That	O
'	O
s	O
good	O
news	O
,	O
right	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
agree	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
relief	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
They	O
did	O
find	O
some	O
polyps	B-HISTORY
and	O
they	O
removed	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
benign	B-HISTORY
,	O
so	O
nothing	O
to	O
worry	O
about	O
there	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
this	O
said	O
they	O
removed	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
forgot	O
the	O
name	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
issue	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
fatigue	B-HISTORY
and	O
like	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
things	O
like	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
get	B-HISTORY
tired	I-HISTORY
very	I-HISTORY
easily	I-HISTORY
.	O
I	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
related	O
to	O
something	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
things	O
have	O
been	O
weird	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
even	O
the	O
minor	O
things	O
like	O
I	O
lift	O
two	O
boxes	O
and	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
something	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
worried	O
about	O
?	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
mild	B-HISTORY
iron	I-HISTORY
deficiency	I-HISTORY
.	O
I	O
will	O
work	O
on	O
that	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
don	O
'	O
t	O
worry	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Are	O
you	O
feeling	O
any	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
great	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
medical	B-HISTORY
issue	I-HISTORY
that	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
worried	O
about	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
feels	O
like	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
young	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
all	O
my	O
activities	B-ACTION
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
at	O
A	B-ORGANIZATION
B	I-ORGANIZATION
C	I-ORGANIZATION
D	I-ORGANIZATION
General	I-ORGANIZATION
Hospital	I-ORGANIZATION
today	O
.	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
wasn	O
'	O
t	O
here	O
right	O
now	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
begin	O
,	O
how	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
seventy	O
seven	O
years	O
young	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Which	O
race	B-HISTORY
,	O
and	O
gender	B-HISTORY
do	O
you	O
identify	O
with	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
m	O
an	O
African	O
American	O
woman	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
'	O
s	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
causing	O
you	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
today	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
had	O
this	O
bunion	B-SYMPTOM
on	I-SYMPTOM
my	I-SYMPTOM
foot	I-SYMPTOM
for	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Is	O
the	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
worsening	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
painful	O
,	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
tried	O
to	O
avoid	O
surgery	B-ACTION
for	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
want	O
this	O
bunion	B-SYMPTOM
gone	O
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
How	O
have	O
you	O
managed	O
this	O
bunion	B-SYMPTOM
in	O
the	O
past	O
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
used	O
antiinflammatories	B-HISTORY
,	O
rested	B-ACTION
,	O
changed	O
my	O
activities	B-ACTION
,	O
I	O
'	O
ve	O
done	O
everything	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
pain	B-SYMPTOM
is	O
getting	O
worse	O
and	O
worse	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
it	O
gone	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
or	O
blood	B-SYMPTOM
pressure	I-SYMPTOM
problems	I-SYMPTOM
?	O
Patient	B-PERSON
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
hypertension	B-HISTORY
but	O
no	O
diabetes	B-HISTORY
.	O
Doctor	B-PERSON
:	O
Alright	O
.	O
"	O
